<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Merge</title>
    <link>http://merge.nate601.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Merge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 20:06:17 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://merge.nate601.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Lore Primer</title>
      <link>http://merge.nate601.me/Lore/loreprimer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 11:11:49 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://merge.nate601.me/Lore/loreprimer/</guid>
      <description>In a distant corner of the universe, a mysterious event caused the worlds of magic and technology to collide, creating a new dimension where both coexisted. This dimension, known as &amp;ldquo;The Merge,&amp;rdquo; became a haven for adventurers and outcasts from across the multiverse.
As one of the few beings capable of using both magic and technology, you have stumbled upon The Merge and have been drawn into its wild and dangerous landscape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the Merge!</title>
      <link>http://merge.nate601.me/Getting-Started/1-Welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 21:41:38 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://merge.nate601.me/Getting-Started/1-Welcome/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to The Merge, a dimension where magic and technology coexist in a fragile balance. You are a dimension hopper, one of the few beings capable of using both magic and technology, who has stumbled upon this strange and dangerous world.
In The Merge, you will encounter a variety of creatures, both friendly and hostile, as you explore the vast landscape. Remember, trust is a fragile thing in The Merge, and not everyone can be trusted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mod List</title>
      <link>http://merge.nate601.me/Getting-Started/2-IncludedMods/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 17:34:32 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://merge.nate601.me/Getting-Started/2-IncludedMods/</guid>
      <description>[Forge] Snad Sand makes sugarcane grow faster!! Accelerated Decay Speeds up the leaf decaying process Ad Astra! &amp;ldquo;Live long and prosper, Ad Astra!&amp;rdquo; Advanced Peripherals &amp;ldquo;A Peripheral addon mod for Computercraft 1.16. You can communicate with Refined Storage, Applied Energistics2 or with the whole Minecraft world. Adds things like the Me Bridge, Rs Bridge, the Chat Box and more.&amp;rdquo; AE Additions - ExtraCells2 Fork &amp;ldquo;An Updated Extra Cells 2. Super Storage Cell, Wireless Transceiver, bigger cells(including for ae2 things), bigger cpus and more to come!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Definitions</title>
      <link>http://merge.nate601.me/Lore/definitions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 11:20:40 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://merge.nate601.me/Lore/definitions/</guid>
      <description>The Merge The name of the dimension where the worlds of magic and technology have collided. The merge is home to a variety of creatures and is a haven for adventurers and outcasts from across the multiverse Dimension Hopper A being capable of traversing dimensions and crossing into different worlds. Dimension hoppers are rare and posses unique abilities that allow them to use both magic and technology Great Collision A catastrophic event that occurred in The Merge, causing the worlds of magic and technology to collide and unleashing a wave of chaos and destruction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Download the Pack!</title>
      <link>http://merge.nate601.me/Getting-Started/3-DownloadThePack/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 20:06:17 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://merge.nate601.me/Getting-Started/3-DownloadThePack/</guid>
      <description>Due to rapid updates to the pack, the best way to install the pack is through the Prism Launcher! Download the prism launcher from their website for your platform, and then download the pack from our discord!
The modpack requires that the user download specifically Java 17! No newer version of Java seems to work. Luckily, you can keep your main version of Java separate from the copy of Java 17, and simply point the Prism launcher to a copy of Java 17 for Minecraft!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connect to the Server</title>
      <link>http://merge.nate601.me/Getting-Started/4-GetConnected/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 17:37:05 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://merge.nate601.me/Getting-Started/4-GetConnected/</guid>
      <description>The server connection information should be preloaded in the client, but in the event that it is not this page is provided. If your username is not on the white-list, please let Nathan know so that you can be added!
Primary Endpoint: nate601.me
Secondary Endpoint: mc.nate601.me
Tertiary Endpoint: 192.161.174.159:25565
The server has a DynMap instance available as well!
Click Here!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
