<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lore on The Merge</title>
    <link>http://merge.nate601.me/lore/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lore on The Merge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 11:20:40 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://merge.nate601.me/lore/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Lore Primer</title>
      <link>http://merge.nate601.me/Lore/loreprimer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 11:11:49 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://merge.nate601.me/Lore/loreprimer/</guid>
      <description>In a distant corner of the universe, a mysterious event caused the worlds of magic and technology to collide, creating a new dimension where both coexisted. This dimension, known as &amp;ldquo;The Merge,&amp;rdquo; became a haven for adventurers and outcasts from across the multiverse.
As one of the few beings capable of using both magic and technology, you have stumbled upon The Merge and have been drawn into its wild and dangerous landscape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Definitions</title>
      <link>http://merge.nate601.me/Lore/definitions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 11:20:40 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://merge.nate601.me/Lore/definitions/</guid>
      <description>The Merge The name of the dimension where the worlds of magic and technology have collided. The merge is home to a variety of creatures and is a haven for adventurers and outcasts from across the multiverse Dimension Hopper A being capable of traversing dimensions and crossing into different worlds. Dimension hoppers are rare and posses unique abilities that allow them to use both magic and technology Great Collision A catastrophic event that occurred in The Merge, causing the worlds of magic and technology to collide and unleashing a wave of chaos and destruction.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
